(Leonard:)In our lives?
That-That we're living?
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes. I...
(Sheldon:)Just yesterday, you had
a-a big piece of lettuce
(Sheldon:)stuck in your teeth at lunch.
(Sheldon:)Did I say anything? No.
(Sheldon:)I compromised
(Sheldon:)and kept my mouth shut.
(Sheldon:)Like you should've, because
everyone was laughing at you.
(Leonard:)That is not
a compromise.
(Leonard:)A compromise is me
driving you everywhere
(Leonard:)because you refuse to learn how.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I learned how.
Amy taught me.
What? Then-Then why
don't you do it?
(Sheldon:)Uh, well, it's scary.
(Sheldon:)And sometimes
I get the pedals mixed up.
(Sheldon:)But, more importantly,
driving me to work
(Sheldon:)is one of the things
that gives your life purpose.
(Sheldon:)I can't take that away from you,
(Sheldon:)so... what do I do?